# Vyacheslav Dyaditsyn Intern Front-End Developer

Kremenchuk | +38 (098) 721-21-05 dyaditsyn@gmail.com



I am beginner Front-End Developer with basic knowledge in HTML, CSS, JS and React.

I have experience with working in equipment and process team in Intel Corporation with strong knowledge in Plasma Etching and Vacuum System and manufacturing process.

My responsibility includes but is not limited to sustaining, troubleshooting, and process improvement operations of a Dry Etch toolset while working under pressure, multitasking and prioritizing tasks and challenges.

Also, I have a business travel experience to USA and Ireland for new technology transfer and professional development.

I'm strongly customer-oriented, well-organized and continuously seek to acquire new professional skills through a combination of on-the-job training, instruction-led training and web-based training.

#### **Work Experience:**

### 2016 - 2019: Equipment and Process Engineer, Intel, Kiryat Gat, Israel.

- · Supporting and sustaining the day-to-day operation of specific processes and equipment
- · Support production line 24/7
- · Providing troubleshooting and general support to other areas as needed (Whole segment data analysis and root cause finding for integrative issues, support and training with Fab and VF systems for fresh engineers)
- · Resolving issues relating to quality and output
- · Improving process parameters to match best in class
- · Improving effectiveness and efficiency of operating procedures
- · Data extraction and analysis to root cause issues and providing solutions
- · Resolving real-life problems that arise on a daily basis in relation to safety, quality, cycle time and tool availability using data-driven decision making
- · Managing and configuring Excursion Prevention System

### 2009 - 2012: Sales and warehouse manager at ACE, Jerusalem, Israel.

- · Customer service
- · Managing orders and working with suppliers

### **Education:**

2021: Web Application Front-End Development Course, Appleseeds Academy, On-line, Israel 2012-2016: B.Sc in Mechanical Engineering, "Azrieli College of Engineering", Jerusalem, Israel 2011-2012: Cellular Technician Course, Nasi Technologies College, Ramat Gan, Israel 2009-2011: Computer Science Student, Hadassah Academic College, Jerusalem, Israel

## **Certifications:**

- Basic and Advanced System Operation and Preventive Maintenance of Hitachi Plasma Etching System (TX, USA)
- Advanced English Cert (ILAC Toronto, CA)

Technical Knowledge: HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap, JS, React, Git

**Foreign Languages:** English – advanced, Hebrew – fluent